FOX IN THE SNOW is a cursive handwriting font.

Commercial use is donationware, please visit http://www.rolandhuse.com for that. 

Please contatct me if you have any questions, requests or feedback.

You MAY NOT sell this font or claim them as your own.
You MAY NOT edit or rename this font.
You MAY NOT redistribute this font.


Thank you & I hope you like this font,

Roland

http://www.rolandhuse.com
https://www.facebook.com/pages/Runes-And-Fonts/123221817784772
